const clericalQuizData = [
	{
		id: 14001,
		question: "This is a type of document issued by a seller to a buyer relating to a sale transaction and indicating the products, quantities and prices sold to the buyer.",
		image: "",
		answer: "Sales invoice",
		choices: [
			"Check voucher",
			"Purchase order",
			"Delivery receipt",
			"Transcript of Records"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 14002,
		question: "Which of the following is not a usual document used in a sales company?",
		image: "",
		answer: "Form 137",
		choices: [
			"Check voucher",
			"Delivery receipt",
			"Sales invoice",
			"Purchase order"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 14003,
		question: "One of the responsibilities of a clerical job is answering and tending phone calls. Which is the best way to answer a phone call in a company?",
		image: "",
		answer: "Answer the phone politely and give your department or company name.",
		choices: [
			"Say “Hello,” and wait for the caller to speak.",
			"Run and get a pen and notebook then pick up the phone.",
			"Get the phone and ask them if they have eaten already.",
			"Wait for fellow employees to answer the phone."
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 14004,
		question: "An example of a hard copy document is:",
		image: "",
		answer: "Business letter in a paper ",
		choices: [
			"PDF file letter",
			"Company email message",
			"A business letter saved in USB",
			"The company chat message"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 14005,
		question: "What does a CC means in an email message?",
		image: "",
		answer: "Copy furnished",
		choices: [
			"Copy sent",
			"Crowd control",
			"Copy cat",
			"Client copy"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 14006,
		question: "Which computer program should you go if you want to email a company?",
		image: "",
		answer: "Outlook",
		choices: [
			"Word",
			"Excel",
			"Access",
			"Powerpoint"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 14007,
		question: "This is a telephonic transmission of scanned documents of texts and images to a telephone number connected to a printer.",
		image: "",
		answer: "Fax Machine",
		choices: [
			"Photocopying machine",
			"Scanner",
			"Typewriter",
			"Inkjet Printer"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 14008,
		question: "The chief financial officer is responsible for the financial matters and financial management of a corporation, she is also known as the _______.",
		image: "",
		answer: "Treasurer",
		choices: [
			"Auditor",
			"Secretary",
			"Chief Executive Officer",
			"Manager"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 14009,
		question: "Which department of a company is responsible for cash register operations and payment processing?",
		image: "",
		answer: "Cashier",
		choices: [
			"Chief Executive Officer",
			"Billing",
			"Accounting",
			"Budget"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 14010,
		question: "Your boss asked you to send her a soft copy of your latest résumé. An example of a soft copy is:",
		image: "",
		answer: "A copy saved in a computer and sent through email",
		choices: [
			"A print out copy usually in a paper",
			"Original copy written in a paper",
			"A black and white copy sent in person",
			"A copy from a Xerox machine"
		],
		guide: ""
	}
]

export default clericalQuizData;